<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FallenAngels</string>
    <string name="get_started">Get Started >></string>
    <string name="ask_sign_in">Wish to sign in?</string>
    <string name="log_in"><u>Log in here</u></string>
    <string name="forgot_pass"><u>Forgot password</u></string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="create_acc">Create Account</string>
    <string name="already_have_acc">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>

    <!--- TODO: Register Page -->
    <string name="account_created">Your account has been created.</string>
    <string name="verify_email">A verification link has been sent to your email. Please verify your account before logging in.</string>
    <string name="change_password">If you would like to change your password then please enter your email. A reset link will be sent.</string>

    <!--- TODO: Home Page -->
    <string name="latest_news">Latest News</string>
    <string name="covid_19">Covid-19 Miracle for our rescues.</string>
    <string name="home_1">At the Government announcement of the National Lockdown we realised we were in a desperate situation with over 350 dogs at the Farm and no way to feed them or care for them without our usual visitors or funds.</string>
    <string name="home_2">Our lockdown foster program was the first in our history and by March 26th over 200 dogs left the farm to go to their foster homes. With the addition of new litters, new rescues and pregnant mommies, that number quickly grew to approximately 275 dogs and puppies in foster care.</string>
    <string name="home_3">Since late March a little over 150 dogs that were in foster care have been adopted, half of those were young dogs or puppies but 50 % were mature adults dogs and 10 % were dogs with medical and behavioral issues.</string>
    <string name="home_4">That means that 77 dogs that would normally never have had a chance at the Farm, have found a home due to having been in Foster care. That is huge and we are immensely grateful to our fosters and adopters alike. We still have about 125 dogs in foster care, 25 of those are puppies that will or have already been adopted. Out of the 100 remaining dogs about half are potential foster fails, have applications or are with fosters that can keep them indefinitely.</string>
    <string name="home_5">All in all this has been a huge success and we would like to thank all of you for making this happen. Please join our Fallen Angels Lockdown Fosters Facebook page if you would like to follow our foster dogs and their amazing journeys.</string>
    <string name="home_6">For most of them, their story has just begun!</string>
    <string name="home_7">Map to Fallen Angels Pet Rescue Farm. (Please do not use Google Maps)</string>
    <string name="home_8">SOUTH AFRICA’S FALLEN ANGELS WIN FIRST BRIAN DAVIES AWARD FOR ANIMAL WELFARE</string>
    <string name="home_9">Named after legendary animal welfare pioneer Brian Davies, The Brian Davies Award is a new annual award made to an animal welfare organisation that has managed to significantly help animals, in difficult and challenging circumstances. It carries a $10,000.00 prize.</string>
    <string name="home_10">Finalists came from Greece, Uruguay and South Africa. Network for Animals (NFA) organised the awards and asked supporters to vote for the most deserving. More than 10,000 people voted.</string>
    <string name="home_11">Fallen Angels is a group of women who venture into South Africa’s poverty-stricken and lawless townships to treat, rescue and rehome street dogs. Their Fallen Angels shelter in the Western Cape now cares for 328 dogs.</string>
    <string name="home_12">Testimonials</string>
    <string name="home_13">“I went to visit today and I was struck by the friendliness of the staff and the lovely happy condition of the dogs. such a happy atmosphere all round. awesome bunch!”</string>
    <string name="home_14">- Jackie Wernberg</string>
    <string name="home_15">"Well done ladies. It was a fantastical day at Willowbridge yesterday. You are passionate caring amazing people"</string>
    <string name="home_16">- Adrian Hochman</string>
    <string name="home_17">Such an amazing shelter! We have adopted a doggo from here in the past &amp; he has grown so beautifully, we couldn"'"t imagine life without him!!! The love &amp; care you give these animals is amazing. keep up the good work! ♡"</string>
    <string name="home_18">- Linzey Marais</string>
    <string name="home_19">"We visited for the first time today and I just wanted to take all of the doggies home with me! Keep up the amazing heartwarming work you guys are doing and we WILL be back"</string>
    <string name="home_20">- Jean Pappas</string>
    <string name="home_21">"Visited today &amp; all the dogs are well looked after and happy...even got to play with a couple of them in the field..definitely worth a visit."</string>
    <string name="home_22">- Annie Steyn</string>
    <string name="home_23">"I volunteered at Fallen Angels this week with one of my friends and I can honestly say I had the time of my life. The farm-staff are extremely friendly and are doing such an incredibly good job at looking after those animals. They’re as happy as shelter animals can be. Charmaine, Craig and Princess Bonnie are the friendliest faces to see on that farm!"</string>
    <string name="home_24">- Kelly Hogg</string>
    <string name="home_25">"We just adopted a beautiful staffie from fallen angels. They did all the right things. Home inspection, introduction to kids, taken the time to match him for all the right reasons. Well done..."</string>
    <string name="home_26">- Warren Herman</string>
    <string name="home_27">"We have never met such caring people before. You can tell everyone there puts their animals first - making sure they are cared for correctly. Thank you for the wonderful advice and most of all for our beautiful new family member Phoenix"</string>
    <string name="home_28">- Debbie Farrel</string>
    <string name="home_29">"These people do such an amazing job with what little they have, Lifesavers for our furry friends."</string>
    <string name="home_30">- David Engelbrecht</string>
    <string name="home_31">"Thank you so much for our precious Angel we adore him and thank you to all involved especially Stef who patiently helped us match our Roxy to Benji - they are inseparable now. Really would encourage anyone to support this wonderful organization ❤"</string>
    <string name="home_32">- Linda Durla</string>
    <string name="home_33">"I have never seen such a well organised pet rescue institution in my life and my own sister runs a rescue shelter. The friendliest, most helpful staff with an amazing amount of knowledge, expertise, love and care about and for all the incredible animals on the farm. Keep up the heavenly work and thank you for taking care of all our furry, four-legged angels."</string>
    <string name="home_34">- Fred Henriques</string>
    <string name="home_35">Furry Angel Power</string>
    <string name="home_36">Our furry angels deserve and get only love, food, tenderness and care from our well trained staff. In fact, our staff live with most of our dogs so as to establish a bond with our angels like at no other rescue organisation. This makes for a mutual bond between our staff and the beautiful creatures that we can all love and save.</string>
    <string name="home_37">Email: info@fallenangels.org.za</string>
    <string name="home_38">Registered Charity: NPO 175-638</string>
    <string name="home_39">PBO Number: 9300 666 72</string>
    <string name="home_40"><u>Terms of Use</u></string>
    <string name="home_41"><u>Privacy Policy</u></string>
    <string name="thanks_heroes">Thanks To Our Heroes</string>

    <!--- TODO: Volunteer Page -->
    <string name="vol_1">Get Involved</string>
    <string name="vol_2">There are so many ways that you can help our animals. We could not do what we do without all our amazing volunteers. Become part of the Fallen Angels team today!</string>
    <string name="vol_3">Fundraising</string>
    <string name="vol_4">Raise money for charity and help us care for sick, abandoned and unwanted pets. You can do anything, from challenging yourself with a sponsored run to organising a tea party! Fundraisers are one of the most effective ways to spread the word about us, and raise money at the same time. Fundraising for Fallen Angels Pet Rescue is a very rewarding experience. Not only will you be helping sick, injured and homeless pets but you will have a great time doing it! Whatever event or challenge you decide to organise or take part in, we’ll support you in every way that we can. Fundraising is a great way to gain new skills and meet friends. On top of that, fundraisers are tax deductible and a great way to show awareness of the cause through your company. 100% of our donations go towards helping our animals find better lives.</string>
    <string name="vol_5">Some Ideas</string>
    <string name="vol_6">Why not order a collection box for the reception at your work or ask if you can put one in your local pub, newsagent or vet? Bake some cakes and sell them at work, school or to your friends Have a swear box in your office, or pick a popular word instead and charge everyone that says it Hold a sponsored ‘give something up’ day. Friends and colleagues could give up chocolate, tea or even talking! Hold a lunchtime quiz at work or school Why not do the washing up for a week and ask for a donation? Hold a ‘Come Dine with Me night at home with your friend or family and charge them to dine</string>
    <string name="vol_7">Organising an Event</string>
    <string name="vol_8">We’d love for you to organise your own fundraising event for us and we’ll do what we can to support you. There are lots of different events you can hold, and here are a few ideas to get your imagination flowing!</string>
    <string name="vol_9">Fun dog show</string>
    <string name="vol_10">Coffee morning</string>
    <string name="vol_11">Dress down day</string>
    <string name="vol_12">Karaoke</string>
    <string name="vol_13">Evening quiz night</string>
    <string name="vol_14">Jumble sale</string>
    <string name="vol_15">Tea party</string>
    <string name="vol_16">Fallen Angels Charity Shop</string>
    <string name="vol_17">Are you cleaning out your closet or redecorating your home and have unwanted items? Please think of us. Everything that you think can aid us in raising funds for Fallen Angels is welcome at our charity shop! We gratefully accept anything resalable or usable, for example:</string>
    <string name="vol_18">Clothing</string>
    <string name="vol_19">Bric-A-Brac and household items</string>
    <string name="vol_20">Jewellery &amp; branded items</string>
    <string name="vol_21">Linens &amp; electricals</string>
    <string name="vol_22">Books &amp; media (CDs and DVDs)</string>
    <string name="vol_23">Coats, shoes &amp; bags</string>
    <string name="vol_24">All of the money raised by us selling your clothes in our Blue Cross shops will go towards helping pets.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Our Mission Page -->
    <string name="miss_1">Our Mission</string>
    <string name="miss_2">Our main mission is to save and improve the living conditions of animals in their immediate surroundings, while maintaining their rehabilitation. This may involve re-homing animals who are unwanted, unloved or lost (mostly focusing on township animals, but not limited to). Ultimately the rehabilitation of animals will involve children, which will then act as therapy for both the children and the animals.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Gallery Page -->
    <string name="gall_1">Happy Homings</string>
    <string name="gall_2">Some of our furbabies in their very own, forever homes. This is what melts our hearts</string>
    <string name="gall_3">Before &amp; After</string>
    <string name="gall_4">Amazing what patience, love, nutrition and vet care can do ! Especially with your support and donations.</string>
    <string name="gall_5">Adoption Days</string>
    <string name="gall_6">Come for cuddles at our weekend adoption days. Keep an eye on our facebook page for where we are.</string>
    <string name="gall_7">Dog Walkers</string>
    <string name="gall_8">Our amazing doggy bootcamp volunteers. Join them every weekend bright and early on the farm.</string>
    <string name="gall_9">Farm Visitors</string>
    <string name="gall_10">Bring the kids and come spend some time with our doggies on our farm.</string>
    <string name="gall_11">Outreach Program</string>
    <string name="gall_12">Our Outreach Program entails partnering up with "Network For Animals" and provides us the opportunity to visit empoverished areas providing free, veterinary care, yummy food and rescue for animals in need. We also visit schools and educate children on pet care.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Events Page -->
    <string name="events_1">Nelson Mandela Days</string>
    <string name="events_2">Our annual Nelson Mandela Day functions are held at Fallen Angels Pet Rescue and embody the true spirit of South African generosity.</string>
    <string name="events_3">Doggy Christmas</string>
    <string name="events_4">Our annual Doggy Christmas Party, held at Fallen Angels Pet Rescue, is an extraordinary site to see. Come experience our unique doggy, gift unwrapping</string>

    <!-- TODO: Contact Page -->
    <string name="con_1">Get in Touch</string>
    <string name="con_2">Portion 25/19 of the farm Kleine Zoute Rivier 1063</string>
    <string name="con_3">Melkbosstrand. 7441</string>
    <string name="con_4">info@fallenangels.org.za</string>
    <string name="con_5">Tel:</string>
    <string name="con_6">084 482 0290 Office Hours</string>
    <string name="con_7">076 993 9670 (Shireen)</string>

    <!-- TODO: About Us Page -->
    <!-- TODO: Check out, coloured text is giving an error -->
    <string name="about_1">Fallen Angels Pet Rescue is a registered NPO (NPO 175-638) focusing on the rescue, rehabilitation and rehoming of domestic animals. Any animal that is forgotten, abandoned (abused), lost, lonely, emaciated and neglected <b><font fgcolor='#EA2F69'>(FALLEN)</font></b> is considered to be a Fallen Angel &amp; therefore part of the focus area of this organisation. Through animal therapy they aim to assist in healing the broken souls of any <b>\"<font fgcolor='#EA2F69'>FALLEN Angels</font>\"</b> they are financially able to assist.</string>
    <string name="about_2">Fallen Angels Pet Rescue was founded in February 2014 by three devoted people; already active within the animal rescue and rehabilitation circuits.</string>
    <string name="about_3">We are situated in Melkbosstrand and we work hard to make sure that all the animals in our care get the love, attention and adoration that they deserve. We have many volunteers that help, which we are all too grateful for. Our aim to make sure that the animals in our care get homes that will give them the comfort that they deserve. It"'"s been a long and hard journey, but one that is worth it every day.</string>
    <string name="about_4">The <b><font fgcolor='#EA2F69'>"'"FALLEN"'"</font></b> in Fallen Angels Pet Rescue stands for
        <b><font fgcolor='#EA2F69'>F</font></b>orgotten,
        <b><font fgcolor='#EA2F69'>A</font></b>bandoned (Abused),
        <b><font fgcolor='#EA2F69'>L</font></b>ost,
        <b><font fgcolor='#EA2F69'>L</font></b>onely,
        <b><font fgcolor='#EA2F69'>E</font></b>maciated and
        <b><font fgcolor='#EA2F69'>N</font></b>eglected.
        Any animal that falls under these categories is considered a ‘Fallen Angel’ and thus falls within the area of importance for this organisation.</string>
    <string name="about_5">Furry Angel Power</string>
    <string name="about_6">Our furry angels deserve and get only love, food, tenderness and care from our well trained staff. In fact, our staff live with most of our dogs so as to establish a bond with our angels like at no other rescue organisation. This makes for a mutual bond between our staff and the beautiful creatures that we can all love and save.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Other strings -->
    <string name="acc_settings">Please sign in or create an account to continue</string>
    <string name="main_page">These gorgeous furbabies are looking for their very own, forever homes. If interested, select a furbaby and proceed with the following steps.</string>
    <string name="view_dog">Looking to adopt or foster? Select one of the options below!</string>
    <string name="back"><u>Back</u></string>
    <string name="fallen_angels">Fallen Angels</string>
    <string name="adopt_application">Adoption Application</string>
    <string name="adopt_fee1">ADOPTION FEE FOR ADULT CATS AND DOGS IS R1000</string>
    <string name="adopt_fee2">ADOPTION FEE FOR PUPPIES AND KITTENS 0-12 IS R1250</string>
    <string name="adopt_fee3">TO BE PAID INTO OUR ACCOUNT PRIOR TO THE PET"'"S ARRIVAL</string>

    <!-- TODO: Adoption Form -->
    <string name="question1">Fur Angel"'"s Name FIRST/SECOND CHOICE</string>
    <string name="question2">Your Name and Surname</string>
    <string name="question3">Address where pet will live (Address)</string>
    <string name="question4">Contact Number</string>
    <string name="question5">Contact Email Address</string>
    <string name="question6">I.D. Number</string>
    <string name="question7">Would you like to be on our mailing list?</string>
    <string name="question8">Ages of children staying in your home?</string>
    <string name="question9">Do you have any other Animals? How Many?</string>
    <string name="question10">Age(s) of your other animals</string>
    <string name="question11">Gender(s) of your other animals</string>
    <string name="question12">How many of your animals are sterilised?</string>
    <string name="question13">If not sterilised, please provide a reason</string>
    <string name="question14">Did any of your animals have a litter before sterilisation?</string>
    <string name="question15">Are your pets (cats &amp; dogs) fully vaccinated?</string>
    <string name="question16">What diet are your pets on?</string>
    <string name="question17">Quantity hours pet would be alone for during the day?</string>
    <string name="question18">If someone is at home during the day, who are they and for how long?</string>
    <string name="question19">Why do you want to Adopt this pet?</string>
    <string name="question20">Have you ever surrendered your animal to a rescue org or given a pet away? If so, why?</string>
    <string name="question21">What happened with your previous pets?</string>
    <string name="question22">Have any of your companions gone missing?</string>
    <string name="question23">Are you prepared to provide a PERMANENT home for the duration of this animal"'"s life?</string>
    <string name="question24">Are you willing to teach your pet about digging, chewing, potty training, etc?</string>
    <string name="question25">Who is responsible for your pets when you go on holiday?</string>
    <string name="question26">What will happen to your pets should your circumstances change? i.e., Loss of job / move into a place that does not allow animals? Can you appoint God Parents for your pet?</string>
    <string name="question27">Where will the dog/cat sleep at night?</string>
    <string name="question28">If outside, what shelter will be provided?</string>
    <string name="question29">If animal will sleep outside, will they be allowed inside and when?</string>
    <string name="question30">Do you have a FENCED / GATED yard?</string>
    <string name="question31">Do you have a pool. If YES, is the pool secure?</string>
    <string name="question32">How often will feeding take place?</string>
    <string name="question33">What size garden will the animal have?</string>
    <string name="question34">Do you have time to play, walk &amp; groom your dog/cat on a daily basis?</string>
    <string name="question35">Have any animal died on your premises due to Parvo / Distemper? If so, how long ago?</string>
    <string name="question36">Are you able to provide Vet care, quality pet food, &amp; grooming for your pet?</string>
    <string name="question37">Type of housing?</string>
    <string name="question38">Do you own or rent?</string>
    <string name="question39">Do you understand that your pet must be vaccinated yearly, dewormed every 6 months and be treated for ticks and fleas every month (at your own cost)?</string>
    <string name="question40">Do you understand that your pet MUST be sterilised at the age of 6 months old?</string>

    <string name="ref1">REF 1:</string>
    <string name="ref2">REF 2:</string>
    <string name="Name">Name</string>
    <string name="relationship_to_you">Relationship to you</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="cell_landline">Cell and Landline</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>

    <string name="signed_on_the">Signed on the</string>
    <string name="day_of">day of</string>
    <string name="year">202</string>
    <string name="at">at</string>
    <string name="app_signature">Applicant"'"s signature:</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full name:</string>
    <string name="thank_you">THANK YOU FOR CHANGING THIS FUR ANGEL"'"S WORLD!!</string>
    <string name="congrats">CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR SUCCESSFUL APPLICATION!</string>

    <!-- Terms and conditions -->


    <!-- TODO: Foster Form -->
    <string name="f_question1"></string>
    <string name="f_question2"></string>
    <string name="f_question3"></string>
    <string name="f_question4"></string>
    <string name="f_question5"></string>
    <string name="f_question6"></string>
    <string name="f_question7"></string>
    <string name="f_question8"></string>
    <string name="f_question9"></string>
    <string name="f_question10"></string>
    <string name="f_question11"></string>
    <string name="f_question12"></string>
    <string name="f_question13"></string>
    <string name="f_question14"></string>
    <string name="f_question15"></string>
    <string name="f_question16"></string>
    <string name="f_question17"></string>
    <string name="f_question18"></string>
    <string name="f_question19"></string>
    <string name="f_question20"></string>
    <string name="f_question21"></string>
    <string name="f_question22"></string>
    <string name="f_question23"></string>
    <string name="f_question24"></string>
    <string name="f_question25"></string>
    <string name="f_question26"></string>
    <string name="f_question27"></string>
    <string name="f_question28"></string>
    <string name="f_question29"></string>
    <string name="f_question30"></string>
    <string name="f_question31"></string>
    <string name="f_question32"></string>
    <string name="f_question33"></string>
    <string name="f_question34"></string>
    <string name="f_question35"></string>

    <!-- TODO: Foster and Adoption forms -->


    <!-- TODO: Remove -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>